(Sheldon:)I'm sorry for your loss.
(Sheldon:)But you're not the only one
whose day has been a disaster.
(Stuart:)That could have killed me.
(Stuart:)I can't catch a break.
(Leonard:)I haven't heard from Sheldon
in a while. You think he's okay?
(Penny:)Oh, I'm sure he's fine.
I'm gonna see where he ls.
(Penny:)How?
(Leonard:)I know his password,
so I can track his phone.
(Penny:)You do that?
(Leonard:)Not always, but ever since
he wandered off at the swap meet
(Leonard:)chasing a balloon, I get worried.
(Penny:)He can take care of himself.
(Penny:)Look, we went over stranger danger
and gave him that whistle.
(Leonard:)That's weird.
(Raj:)-What?
-He's at the train station.
(Penny:)So? He loves trains.
(Leonard:)It's dark out and he's alone,
I don't like it. Let's go get him.
Oh, it's sweet how you look out
for him. You're a good guy.
(Leonard:)Not just that. My mother would kill
me if I let something happen to him.